### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/naman-grover-ab6641167 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Leadership

Management

Python (Programming Language)

## Languages

English (Professional Working)

#### Certifications

Git started with GitHub Machine Learning Python for Developers

# Naman Grover

Machine Learning Engineer at Blacknet

East Delhi, Delhi, India

## Summary

Growth is an underlying passion that drives my programming and entrepreneurial spirit.

Python|django developer and a machine learning enthusiast. Let's connect to see where i can help, be it long term projects, or short term experiences.

# Experience

GeeksforGeeks
Technical Content Writer
May 2019 - Present (11 months)

Coding Club
Organizer
August 2018 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Mekvahan Deep Learning Developer Intern July 2019 - August 2019 (2 months) New Delhi Area, India

## Education

Guru Tegh Bahadur Institute Of Technology BTech - Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

St Andrews Scots Senior Secondary School 10+2